Tufts University Staff Association (TUSA) Records UA026
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts University Staff Association (TUSA) Records
1984 -- 1992
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts University Staff Association
UA026
0.25 Linear Feet 1 box
Arrangement
This collection is organized in one series: Subject Files.
Related Materials
The Tufts University Staff Association Newsletter are located in UP026 Tufts University Staff Association Newsletter, 1985-1992.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains correspondence, memoranda, a survey, schedules, fliers, and a constitution pertaining to the Tufts University Staff Association from 1984-1992.
Related Materials
UP026, Tufts University Staff Association Newsletter, DCA
Biographical / Historical
Tufts University Support Staff Association was formed in 1983. It changed its name to Tufts University Staff Association in 1988. They organized to serve as an advocate for issues of concern for Tufts staff members, to build a communication network among staff in all areas of the University, and to provide support, guidance and information on work-related issues and problems to fellow staff employees at Tufts University. As advocates of staff concerns, they were not officially recognized by Tufts University. Nor were they represented in any decision-making entity. Tufts University Staff Association also sponsored programs and events to support socializing and making friends and professional contacts within the Tufts community.
Tufts University Staff Association ceased to exist after 1992.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Employment and Human Resources
- Subject Files, 1984 -- 1992; UA026.001; 0.25 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series of the Tufts University Staff Association records contains correspondence, memorandum, a survey, schedules, fliers, and a constitution pertaining to the Tufts University Staff Association. The association was started in 1984 and was called Tufts University Support Staff Association which became Tufts University Staff Association in 1989.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Constitution, 1992; UA026.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence Between TUSA Members, 1991; UA026.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Fliers, 1992; UA026.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Memorandum to All Exempt and Non-exempt Office Support Staff, 1984; UA026.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Memorandum to TUSA Board Members, 1991; UA026.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Memorandum to TUSA Members, 1991; UA026.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - TUSA Board Meeting Minutes, 1991; UA026.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - TUSA Meetings Schedule, 1991; UA026.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - TUSA Staff Personnel Survey, 1989; UA026.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - TUSSA (Tufts University Support Staff Association) Membership Drive, 1985; UA026.001.001.00010 (Box 1)